孩儿们 大二那年\n当Lily阿姨放完春假回来时
Marshall叔叔在机场给了她一份惊喜
Uncle Marshall surprised\nher at the airport.
她也回赠给他一份惊喜\n带回了6罐当地酿造的啤酒
And she surprised him with a\nsix-pack of locally brewed beer.
Fort Lauger Dale!
听说过吧?
Fort Lau-ger-Dale!\nGet it?
随之一个新的惯例形成了
And with that, a ritual was born.
接下来的11年里 他俩不管飞去哪里...
For the next 11 years, whenever\neither of them would fly anywhere...
Minne-Cider! 听说过吧?
Minne-Cider! Get it?
重聚老是以专职司机的帽子和6罐啤酒来庆祝
the reunion was always commemorated with a chauffeur\nsign and a six-pack from wherever they'd been.
Aspen Yards Ale! 听说过吧?
Aspen Yards Ale! Get it?
事实上 没
Actually,no.
我也是 还指望你知道呢
Me,neither. I was hoping you would.
但2009年一月的一个晚上\n意想不到的事发生了
But then,one night in January of\n2009, the unthinkable happened.
- 我不去接她了\n- 什么?
- I'm not picking her up.\n- What?
Lily不会想我坐着出租翻山越岭地去机场\n只是为了跋山涉水地坐着回来
Lily doesn't want me taking a cab all the way to the\nairport just to take a cab all the way back,you know?
- 那6罐啤酒咋办?
- Ted...\n- But the six-pack\nthing. - Ted...
那只是我们年轻时玩玩的\n现在我们过了那年龄了
that stuff was fun when we were\nyounger, but we've grown past that.
随着我们成熟 我们的爱情也成熟了
As we mature,the\nrelationship matures with us.
但...我是说 在我们看来你们是\n那么有情趣的一对 那么如胶似漆
But... I mean, you guys are such an inspiration to\nthe rest of us,how you're so devoted and connected.
看到你们俩 我才知道\n这才是真正的人生呀
I look at you guys, and that's\nall I want in the whole world.
Ted 外面有两个女大学生 看上去很好把哦!
Ted,there's two college girls\noutside,and they look easy!
亚利桑那啊 我老是想看看\n亚利桑那的驾驶执照长啥样
So,Arizona-- you know, I- I've always wanted to\nsee what an Arizona driver's license looks like.
- 我已经用过这招了 老兄 她们年满21了 没事的 \n- 太好啦
- I already ran that play, bro. They're 21. We're good.\n- Thank God.
啥风把你们吹到镇上的?
So,um, what brings you guys to town?
我们的乐队来这演出
Our band's got a gig.
你们是乐队里的?\n嘿 或许我们能来看你们表演
Oh,you're in a band? Hey,maybe\nwe'll come see you play.
失陪一下
Excuse us for a sec.
Ted 你到底哪根筋不对?\n我们不去看她们表演
Ted,what the hell is the matter with\nyou? We're not gonna go see them play.
为啥不?
Why not?
如果去看她们表演
If we see them play, we're no\nbetter than the bleach-blonde bimbos
我们比那些在Van Halen音乐会上\n露着胸部招摇过市的金发女人好不到哪去
who flash their boobs\nat a Van Halen concert.
嗯 但事后那些女孩没和Van Halen做爱吗?
Yeah,but don't those girls get to\nhave sex with Van Halen after the show?
如果你想和Van Halen做爱\nTed 你一个人去吧
If you want to have sex with Van\nHalen, do it on your own time,Ted.
我们不能说"或许能来看你们表演"
We are not the maybe-we-can-come-\nsee-you-play guys.
我们与众不同 是她们所向往的彬彬有礼的老男人
We're the other guys, the older guys who never\nshowed up and whose approval they now crave.
那么我们是她们老爸?
So we're their dads?
- 就是这样\n- 好吧
- Exactly.\n- Okay.
我们有重要会议要开 所以恐怕来不了
It's a big meeting, so I don't\nthink we're gonna make it.
或许下次吧 孩子们
Maybe next time,kiddos.
但如果你们想在演出完后见面\n或许我们能交换下电话号码
But if you guys want to meet up after your\nshow, maybe we could exchange numbers...
失陪一下
Excuse us for a minute.
Ted 你脑抽了吗?
Ted,have you gone completely insane?
我们不能要她们的号码
We don't want their phone numbers.
是 我不知道我在干嘛 我想我紧张得昏头了
Yeah. I don't know what I was\ndoing. I guess I panicked out there.
一旦和小妞交换了号码\n她们就可能打电话取消约会
When you exchange numbers with a chick you\ngive them the ability to call and cancel.
如果没电话号码 她们就得来赴约
If you set a date without a\nnumber, they have to show up.
没有后路和我们上床!
Check and mate!
只需把手指这样
The only digits I need are these.
爽
Honka.
你还是她们老爸吗?
Are you still their dad?
明晚10:00这儿碰面咋样?
So,why don't we just meet here\ntomorrow night around 10:00.
我觉得应该会下雪
I think it's supposed to snow.
要是暴雪咋办?
What do we do if there's a blizzard?
无所谓 我们会在这儿
Either way, we'll be here.
没问题\n(snow中有no的音)
"Snow" problem.
失陪最后一下
Excuse us just one last second.
又咋了?
What is the problem now?
这个说得好
Nice one.
好吧 我们明晚见啦
All right,we'll see you tomorrow night.
- 好的\n- 太棒了!
- Totally.\n- Awesome!
"好的 太棒了!"
"Totally. Awesome!"
伙计 这些大学小妞好蠢啊
Man,these college chicks sound stupid.
- 蠢透了\n- 真棒
- Totally.\n- Awesome.
明晚 整装待发 会非常带劲的!
So,here's the thing: tomorrow night,\ndress to move; it's gonna be a mess!
我还是觉得我们应该问她们号码
I still think we should've\ngotten their numbers.
你老是杞人忧天
You always assume\nsomething is gonna go wrong.
Ted 我向你保证 不会出什么问题的
Ted,I promise you,\nnothing is gonna go wrong.
嘿 开始下雪啦
Hey,it's starting to snow.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第13集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode13
孩儿们 09年第一场雪来的特别猛
Kids,the blizzard of '09 was a monster.
整整下了3天 随之发生了3段小插曲
It snowed for three days straight,\nwhich led to three amazing stories.
先说我和Barney
I'll start with me and Barney.
外面暴雪肆虐啊
It's pretty nasty out there.
我觉得她们不会来
I don't think they're coming.
她们肯定会来 必须来
Of course they're coming. They have to.
如果我能搞到其中一个妞\n我就能赢泡学生妞比赛
If I can land just one of these\ngirls, I'll have party school bingo.
得了吧 Ted 这儿就你一个
Come on,Ted. You're the only one here.
不好意思 那啥是泡学生妞比赛啊?
Sorry. What's party school bingo?
每年花花公子杂志都会公布一份美女大学排行榜
Every year, Playboyreleases a list of\nthe top party schools in the country.
我取了前25位 我还做了张
I take the top 25, and I make up...
宾戈游戏卡
a bingo card.
钓上亚利桑那工学院的就行了 真疯狂啊
All I need is Arizona\nTech, which is crazy.
游戏规则就是填空格子
In league play, that would\nnormally be designated a free space.
有多少人参加泡学生妞比赛啊?
So,uh,how many people are in on\nthis party school bingo thing?
就我一个
Oh,it's just me.
那到底是啥意思?
So what's the point,then?
就是说要一排上填满5个格子
The point is to get five in a row.
当你一排填满5格时 你会得到啥?
And what do you get when\nyou get five in a row?
我就赢了
I get bingo.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming by.
我把恒温器捣鼓了一小时才发现那是对讲机
I monkeyed around with the thermostat for about\nan hour before I realized it was the intercom.
嗯 我听到你在楼下骂脏话
Yeah,I heard you swearing downstairs.
嘿 Lily的航班今晚就到\n你真的不去接她了?
Hey,so,uh, Lily's flight's coming in tonight--\nyou're really not gonna go pick her up?
Robin Robin 就像我说的 随着我们成熟
Robin,Robin,like I said, as we mature,
我们的爱情也成熟了
our relationship matures with us.
嗯 我了解你老婆\n无论如何 她都会带6罐啤酒回来
Yeah,well,if I know your wife, she's\ngonna get you that six-pack anyway.
Marshall? Marshall?\nMarshall? Marshall?
Puget Stout 最精湛的西雅图酿酒工艺
Puget Stout. A most\nexquisite Seattle microbrew.
说起6块...\n（6块腹肌）
And speaking of six-packs...
- 你去干吗?\n- 我去机场
- What are you doing?\n- I'm going to the airport.
我咋会这么蠢?
How could I be so stupid?
她肯定带给我6罐啤酒的!
Of course she's bringing me a six-pack!
这次 我没带给他6罐啤酒
But this time,I didn't\nbring him a six-pack.
因为 随着我们成熟 爱情也成熟了
Because... as we mature,the\nrelationship matures with us.
貌似他是个不错的年轻人呢
Well,he sounds like a nice young man.
我敢打赌 无论如何\n他会给你个惊喜 接你回家的
I'll bet he surprises you\nand picks you up anyway.
宝贝!
Oh,baby!
我的啤酒呢?
Where's my beer?
我们说好不再这么做的
We said we weren't gonna.
带啤酒的人
Someone with beer
我有啤酒
I have beer.
6罐啤酒 而且你的高度对我来说刚刚好
A six-packandyou're an\nappropriate height for me.
我们走吧 新Lily
Let's go,New Lily.
我得弄些啤酒来
Oh,man,I got to get some beer.
乘客们 我是机长
Folks,this is your captain speaking.
看样子我们会提早一小时到达目的地
Looks like we're going to\nbe arriving an hour early.
太棒了!
Yes!
喝光就走 伙计们 我要打烊了
Drink up,boys. I'm closing the bar.
不! 才9:00呀
Whoa,no! It's only 9:00.
这儿很热闹啊 唷!
And this place is ragin',yo!
伙计们 真抱歉\n我得去教堂地窖里盖帆布了
Guys,I'm really sorry, but I got to\ngo set up cots in the church basement.
像这种雪天里得盖两层
It doubles as a shelter\non snowy nights like this.
你个自私鬼!
You selfish bastard!
有两个辣妹要来这和我们碰面
There are two very hot\ngirls coming here to meet us.
你就不能晚点在关门吗?
Can't you just leave the place\nopen a little while longer?
我们会帮你照看的
We'll keep an eye on everything.
你俩? 没门
You two? No way.
你们连开家酒吧最基本的东西都不知道
You wouldn't know the first\nthing about running a bar.
辣妹优先?
Serve the hotties first?
给你钥匙
Here's the keys.
你们的姑娘一旦出现 就帮我关灯锁门
As soon as your girls show up, you\nturn off the lights and you lock up.
我回来时不想看到这儿乱作一团
I don't want to come back here\nand find this place trashed.
哇 真的吗?
Wow,seriously?
我相信你们
I can trust you guys.
想知道拿到MacLaren酒吧的钥匙\n对我们意味着什么吗?
To understand what it meant to\nus to get the keys to MacLaren's,
我就得从几年前说起
I have to take you back a few years
那晚 我说出了每个男人一生中
to the night that I uttered\nfive little words that
都会说的那8个字
every man at some point\nin his life will say.
我们应该买家酒吧
We should buy a bar.
就是 我们应该买家酒吧
Of course,we should buy a bar!
- 我们的确应该买家酒吧\n- 我们的确应该买家酒吧
- We should totally buy a bar.\n- We should totally buy a bar.
我们的酒吧肯定会棒极了
Our bar would be awesome.
老兄 老兄 老兄...
And dude,dude, dude,dude...
酒吧的名字...谜题
the name of our bar... Puzzles.
人总是会奇怪 为啥会叫谜题
People will be like, "Why\nis it called Puzzles?"
这就是我们的谜题
That's the puzzle.
这...真是个好名字!
That is... a great name for a bar!
当然 在Puzzles酒吧 没打烊铃
And also, at Puzzles: no last call.
没打烊铃!
No last call!
每个人都会在那度过人生中最美好的夜晚
Only when every single person is finished\nhaving the greatest night of his or her life
我们把椅子堆在桌上\n然后做3层楼的鸡尾酒瀑布
do we stack the chairs on the table and power\ndown the three-story margarita waterfall.
- 我们应该买家酒吧\n- 我们应该买家酒吧
- We should buy a bar.\n- We should buy a bar.
就像每个男人都会说的豪言壮语
And like the other ill-advised five-word\nsentences every man eventually says in his life...
我能跳那么远
I can jump that far.
我要把她赢回来
I'm gonna win her back.
我能相信你们
I can trust you guys.
我们最终会后悔
we would come to regret it.
我们只是还不知道
We just didn't know it yet.
你到了? 好极了 我马上到
You have it? Awesome--\nI'll be right there.
- Ranjit!（那个常常出现的司机）\n- 你好
- Ranjit!\n- Hello.
我就是Rachel Sondheimer
Uh,I'm Rachel Sondheimer.
等下 Lily
Wait a minute,Lily.
你刚下飞机吗? Marshall呢?
If you are getting off the\nplane,where is Marshall?
你的6罐啤酒呢?
And where is your six-pack?
这就是问题所在\n我得在一小时后到东牧场的Brewniverse
That's the problem. I have to get to\nBrewniverse in East Meadow in an hour.
- 车在那边!\n- 谢谢
- To the Town Car!\n- Oh,thank you.
酒保 3份香槟
Oh,barkeep. Triple Sec.
马上来 调酒师
Coming right up, tap-minder.
吼 吼 嘿!
Hup,hup,oh,hey!
再拿一瓶
We'll get one.
- 上酒\n- 上酒
- Order up.\n- Order up.
再调一杯
We'll get one.
谢天谢地 你们还在这儿
Oh,thank God you're still here.
我不知道你们看没看过星球大战\n外面就像霍斯星球雪地战景一样
I don't know if you guys have ever\nseenStar Wars, but it's like Hoth out there.
小儿科
Dibs.
让我想起过去常和爸爸一起滑雪橇
It reminds me of when I used\nto go sledding with my dad...
在他离开前
before he left.
太小儿科了
And dibs.
呃 要来杯暖身不?
So,uh,can we warm you up with a drink?
当然... 还有 \n我把乐队其他人叫过来这里见面了
Sure... oh,uh,by the way,I invited the\nrest of the band to come and meet us.
我们要不醉无归
We were hoping to get drunk.
要大醉一场 就像我爸以前那样
I meanreallydrunk. Like my dad used to.
太幼稚了 太幼稚了 太幼稚了
Dibsity,dibsity, dibsity.
那好 我想我们可以迟点关门的
Well,I guess we could keep the\nplace open a little bit longer.
不过只能是你们和乐队哦
As long as it's just you and the band.
嗯 Melissa 你们这是啥乐队啊?
Um,Melissa, what kind of band is this?
我们是亚利桑那州工学院战斗鸡军乐队
Oh,we're the Arizona Tech\nFighting Hens Marching Band.
加油 鸡\n（hen也有姑娘和禽兽的意思）
Go,Hens!
然后 你们Barney叔叔\n和我进行了一次心灵交流
And then, your Uncle Barney and I had\none of our telepathic conversations.
哥们儿 立刻把这群家伙赶出去\n不然Carl会杀了我们的
Dude,Carl's gonna kill us if we don't\nkick everyone out of here right now.
Barney 我说真的
Barney,I'm serious.
我们保证过不搞砸这里的
We promised we wouldn't\nmess the place up.
好吧 你说得有道理
All right, I guess you have a point.
开始营业了!
The bar is open!
我还是觉得很傻
I still say this is stupid.
"两人间的感情会随着两人的成熟而成熟"\n突然间就不算数了?
What happened to,"As we mature,\nthe relationship matures with us"?
Lily在"现代心理"看回来的而已
That's just something Lily\nread inPsychology Today.
好啦 她在"时尚Cosmo"看回来的
All right, she read it inCosmo.
好啦 是我在"时尚Cosmo"看回来的
All right,I read it inCosmo.
好啦 我看的是"时尚Cosmo"少女版\n开你的车吧
All right,it was Cosmo\nGirl. Just drive,okay.
我就是不明白 不过是抛弃个小惯例而已\n有什么大不了的
I just don't get why it's such a big deal\nthat one little ritual goes by the wayside.
没这么简单的 好不?
It's not just this,okay?
这关乎我们所有的传统
It's all our little rituals.
你知道以前我一回家会做什么吗?
Do you know what we used to do\nevery day the second I got home?
老兄 我可不想听你讲什么疯猴子性爱
Man,I don't want to hear\nabout your crazy monkey sex.
我们跟彼此述说那天吃了什么
We would tell each other\nwhat we had to eat that day.
两只蛋 一块芝士比萨和素菜
Two eggs,a slice of cheese\npizza and some steamed veggies.
什锦百吉饼 鸡胸肉 \n芹菜杆儿还有一勺花生酱
Everything bagel, chicken breast, some\ncelery sticks and a spoon of peanut butter.
要来疯猴子性爱吗?
Crazy monkey sex?
疯猴子性爱
Crazy monkey sex.
Lily TMI--你说太多啦
(too many informations)\nOh,Lily,TMI-- too\nmany informations.
知道我还想念什么吗?
You know what else I miss?
我们的午饭电话
Our lunchtime phone call.
嘿 宝贝儿 到了午饭时间了 我爱你
Hey,baby,it's lunchtime, and I love you.
原则上我也是这样的
I reciprocate in principle.
不过要提醒你的是 我这边有点过剩
Although with the caveat that there seems\nto be a bit of a surplus here on my end.
才不呢 我爱你多点
No,I love you more.
那要不我们今晚开个房"搞"定这事?
Do we need to get in a room\ntogether and bang this thing out?
这条款听起来不错 \n不过我要调整下我的大纲(内裤)
Those sound like agreeable terms,\nalthough I may need adjust my briefs.
我也爱你
Love you,too.
可是她今天打来时 \n我把它转去了语音邮箱 语音邮箱!
But today when she called, I let\nit go to voice mail. Voice mail!
你怎么能这样?
How could you?
我最想念的是除夕夜的吻
The thing I miss most is kissing\nat midnight on New Year's Eve.
那是新年的传统习俗
It was a New Year's tradition.
可你知道我们今年做了什么吗?
But you know what we did this year?
- 疯猴子性爱?\n- 不是啦
- Crazy monkey sex?\n- No.
这些可爱的 讨人喜欢的传统--很弱智啊
Okay,all these cute,adorable\nlittle rituals-- they're stupid.
告诉彼此吃了什么? \n就像小孩子玩过家家那样
Telling each other what you had to\neat? You're like children playing house.
或者 你觉得很弱智
Well...maybe you just\nthink they're stupid
只是因为你从未试过爱到那个层次而已
because you've never been in a\nrelationship long enough to develop them.
啥?
What?
你根本不懂爱
You don't understand love.
你就像个机器人 见到有人流泪就会说...
Okay,you're like some robot who\nsees a person crying and says...
"为什么那人类在漏油?"
"Why is that human leaking?"
- 是这样吗?\n- 没错
- Is that right?\n- Yeah.
那好...机器人执行"把车停到路边"
Well,then...Robot initiating\npull-over-to-the- side-of-the-road-
"直到那混蛋道歉"指令
until-jackass-apologizes-\nto-me sequence.
我的机器人...好一百万倍
My robot was like, a\nmillion times better.
嘿 厕所的水槽满了
Oh,hey,just so you know, the trough\nin the bathroom is overflowing.
厕所没有水槽
There's no trough in the bathroom.
你刚刚走出来的是厨房
And you just came out of the kitchen.
Ted 金汤利用什么调的?
Ted,what's in a gin and tonic?
金汤利用什么调的?
What's in a gin and tonic?
开酒吧真的糟透了 我们还是关门大吉吧
Okay,running a bar sucks.\nLet's just close up.
不! 不! 不能有打烊铃
No! No! There's no last call.
谜题酒吧 Barney
Puzzles,go for Barney.
好极了 你还在那儿 我五分钟内到
Good. You're still there.\nI'll be there in five.
打烊铃
Last call.
Robin 有部扫雪车开过来了 快上路
Robin,there's a snowplow coming.\nWe have to get back on the road.
你认为相爱的唯一方法是为对方起爱称
You think the only way to be\nin love is to have pet names.
给对方留些弱智小纸条\n又或者是无端端地在暴风雪天气里接人
Or leave each other stupid,little notes or go\ncharging off into a blizzard for no good reason.
说真的 你知道那部扫雪车\n经过会发生什么事吗?
Seriously,do you understand what's\ngoing to happen if that plow comes by?
你知道吗? 你是个装内行的爱情专家
You know what you are?\nYou're a love snob.
拍拖有很多方式的
There's lots of ways\nto be in a relationship,
如果你肯退出\n装内行爱情专家俱乐部就会知道
and you would know that if you ever\nleft your little love snob country club.
我们会被雪埋住 快了
We're going to get buried by\nsnow. That's going to happen.
不 去你的 我才不会坐在这里被人侮辱
No,screw this. I'm not going\nto sit here and be insulted.
不去飞机场了 我们回家
We're not going to the\nairport. We're going home.
发生啥事了?
What just happened?
我们之前打电话订了西雅图自酿啤酒的
We called earlier about\nthe Seattle microbrew.
好在你打电话了
Oh,yeah,good thing you\ncalled when you did.
我就快关门了
I was getting ready to close up.
外面可是世纪风暴
Storm of the century out there.
当然 现在才09年 \n要说世纪风暴还太早了
Of course,it's only '09, so storm of the\ncentury might be a little bit premature.
还是叫它年度风暴吧
Let's say storm of the year.
虽然现在才一月
Although,it is only January.
我们有点急事 所以 现在就要拿啤酒
We're in kind of a hurry,\nso,we'll take the beer now.
你们这对夫妻挺配的
You are a cute couple.
- 谢谢啊\n- 我们不是夫妻
- Thank you.\n- We're not a couple.
上帝保佑 要是真的夫妻就奇怪了
Thank God. That would be weird.
好吧...
Well...
来了 "超音波酒"
here she is. "Supersonic Tonic."
不对 这是一桶 我要的是六瓶装
No. This is a keg. I need a six-pack.
- 我只有这桶了\n- 那就这桶吧
- A keg's all I got.\n- We'll take the keg.
啥? 不要 \n上次有个家伙喝了这桶坐我的车
What? Oh,no. Last time I\nhad one of these in the car,
我最后要用油灰刀才把那些呕渍切下来
I wound up chipping dried vomit\noff the seat with a putty knife.
对不起了 Ranjit 可这是个传统\n我一定要带这桶啤酒给他
I'm sorry,Ranjit, but this is a\nritual and I am bringing him this beer.
前提是你能帮我把它弄到车上
If you could just put it in the car.
我给你50美元
I'll give you 50 bucks.
马上上车
To the Town Car.
Robin 我很抱歉 你不是个机器人
Robin,I'm sorry. You're not a robot.
就算是 你也是个超级先进的型号
If you are,you're, like,an\nincredibly advanced model,
人类在你面前一点机会都没有
and the human race\ndoesn't stand a chance.
你只是不肯把爱表现在\n平时的小习惯上 没事儿
You just don't choose to show your love\nthrough corny rituals, and that's fine.
可我和Lily整天这样可能是因为习惯了\n而且我们不知道其他方式去表达
But maybe the reason Lily and I do is because\nwe always have, and we don't know any other way.
可我唯一知道的是\n如果她独自一人坐在飞机场的话
One thing I do know is that if she's\nthere sitting at the airport alone,
我一定要去接她
I have to go get her.
这是规矩
Those are the rules.
Marshall 闭上眼睛
Marshall,close your eyes.
我不知道你听谁说我喜欢你的 可...
I don't know how you heard any of\nthat as me hitting on you,but...
闭上就好
Just do it.
去接你女人吧
Now let's go get your woman.
来吧来吧
All right,come on.
你不必回家 可是不能留在这里
You don't have to go home,\nbut you can't stay here.
我总想这么说 我是说 在酒吧里
I've always wanted to\nsay that. I mean,in a bar.
我整天在家里这么说
I say it all the time at home.
老兄 总有一天我们会买下个酒吧
Dude,someday we should buy a bar.
那时 绝不能有打烊铃
And when we do, we\narenevergoing to have last call.
Barney 我们说过没有打烊铃的\n不能言而无信啊
Come on,Barney. We said no\nlast call. We've got to mean it.
那 那该怎么办呐? Carl随时会杀回来的
Well,what are we supposed to do?\nCarl's going to be here any minute.
就这么办
Only one thing we can do.
兄弟 开酒吧真是有苦自知啊
Dude,running a bar is a pain in the ass.
我们只需做自己喜欢的就可以了
We should just stick with what we know.
我们该组个乐队
We should start a band.
就该组个乐队!
Of course we should start a band!
怎么会一直都没想到呢?
How have we not started a band yet?
孩子们 漫漫人生中有些事是命中注定的
Kids,sometimes in\nlife the planets align,
所有事情都安排好 时机也很完美
everything links up, and\nyour timing is perfect.
- Marshall?\n- Lily?\n- Marshall?\n- Lily?
可却不是此时
This wasn't one of those times.
她在那儿呢?
Where is she?
- 西雅图\n- 啥?
- Seattle.\n- What?
她的班级取消了 飞机没有起飞
Her flight's canceled.\nIt never took off.
不 不会的 她会打给我的...
No,no,she would've called me and...
嘿 宝贝儿 是我
Hey,baby,it's me.
因为现在暴风雪啊 我的班机取消了\n他们说只能订到周四的票
My flight's been canceled because of some\nsnowstorm and they couldn't rebook me till Thursday,
所以我要在这里留两天了
so I'm stuck here for another two days.
不过现在是午饭时间了 我爱你
But it's lunchtime, and I love you.
正如我所说 这场暴风雪持续了三天
Like I said, this\nwas a three-day storm.
"周二" 我还是觉得这样很傻
****I still say this is stupid.
"周三"
*****
- "周四"\n- 之前打电话订了西雅图自酿啤酒的
- *********\n- Called earlier about the Seattle microbrew.
所以当周二Marshall听到这消息时...
So on Tuesday when Marshall\nheard that message...
她周四才回来
She's not coming in till Thursday.
我们折腾了这么久 而她周四才回来
I mean,we came all the way down here,\nand she's not coming in till Thursday.
我真的太傻了
I feel so stupid.
这样吧 不要告诉Lily今天的事 好吗?
Look,let's just, let's not\ntell Ly about any of this,okay?
特别是你喜欢我那段
Especially the part\nabout you hitting on me.
我才没有喜欢你呢
I didn't hit on you.
就这么说
Exactly.
然后周三
Then on Wednesday...
伙计 真是难以置信\n你开了老大一段路去接人
Oh,man. I can't believe you\ndrove all the way out there.
明天你又要开老大一段路回去了
Now you're just going to turn around and\ndrive all the way out there again tomorrow.
没错 不对
Yeah,no.
嗯 整件事对我来说是个启示
Um,this whole thing was a sign,you know?
是时候抛弃这些旧习惯了
It's time to put that old ritual to bed.
我不去接她了
I'm not going to pick her up.
Robin真的喜欢你?
Robin really hit on you?
兄弟 真的很奇怪
Dude,it was weird.
哥们儿 这派对真的是太棒了!
Bros,this party isawesome!
你们是战斗鸡的好哥们儿
You are true friends\nof the Fighting Hens.
以后有啥事儿 吼一嗓子哈
If you ever need anything,\ndon't hesitate to ask.
那吹笛子的有在约会吗?
Is the flute section seeing anyone?
等等 你真的不打算接她了?
So,wait,you're really\nnot going to pick her up?
真的
Yeah,really.
那新年之吻 午饭电话
So the New Year's kiss,\nthe lunchtime phone calls,
还有"今天吃了啥"那档事 \n你...你就让它这么完了?
the whole "this is what I ate today" thing,\nyou're,you're really letting it all go?
认真的
I really am.
然后到了周四
Which brings us to Thursday.
一块松饼 牛肉三明治 还有一袋薯条
A muffin,a pastrami\nsandwich, and a bag of chips.
我明白午饭时间已经过去很久了\n不过我爱你
And I know it's way past\nlunchtime,but I love you.
与日俱增 我爱你 Lily
More and more each day, I love you,Lily.
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
嗯 等等 那是不是说以后来接你\n都要带支军乐队?
Um,wait, does this mean that I have to bring\na marching band to the airport from now on?
当然
Absolutely,it does.
糟糕
Crap.
加油 鸡!
Go,Hens!
谜题
Puzzles.
这乐队名太棒了
That is a great band name.
嘿 有见过Amanda吗?
Hey,have you seen Amanda?
我赢了!
Bingo!